[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of Hermones cat in the Harry Potter series?", "correct_answer": "Crookshanks", "incorrect_answers": ["Kittywizardodopolis", "Dumbledore", "Squeaks"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Caipirinha takes lime, caster sugar, and Cachaca, or Rum to chill out the citizens of this country.", "correct_answer": "Brazil", "incorrect_answers": ["Cuba", "Mexico", "Hawaii"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What do Lou Gehrig, the four Beatles, Beethoven, Bach and Mr. Spock have in common?", "correct_answer": "They are asteroids.", "incorrect_answers": ["They have stars on the New York City Walk of Fame.", "They are enshrined in the US Hall of Fame in New York City.", "They are stars."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Wedding Crashers, who claimed to be first-team All-State and in which sport?", "correct_answer": "Jeremy, Football", "incorrect_answers": ["Zach, Football", "Todd, Hunting", "John, Hunting"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 1971 film is based on the novel I Am Legend by Richard Matheson.", "correct_answer": "The Omega Man", "incorrect_answers": ["Daughters of Darkness", "Rabid", "The Last Man on Earth"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Between 1997 and 2006, there were how many reported deaths from lightning?", "correct_answer": "437", "incorrect_answers": ["393", "750", "825"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Byzantine church of Hagia Irene was the seat of the Bishop of Constantinople until what year?", "correct_answer": "415", "incorrect_answers": ["738", "404", "564"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Labrador Retriever is considered a medium-sized dog. How much does it weigh when fully grown?", "correct_answer": "55 - 80 pounds", "incorrect_answers": ["65 - 110 pounds", "40 - 55 pounds", "20 - 60 pounds"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which country has the highest population density in the world as of 2008?", "correct_answer": "Monaco", "incorrect_answers": ["Singapore", "China", "India"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Discovery Channel did a real documentary based on the events surrounding The Blair Witch Project prior to the movies release.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of plant is the mulberry?", "correct_answer": "Tree", "incorrect_answers": ["None of these", "Herb", "Shrub"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What elephant species has two fingerlike projections at the end of its trunk?", "correct_answer": "African Elephant", "incorrect_answers": ["Asian Elephant", "All of these", "Sri Lankan Elephant"]}]